blackcaps.co.nz 2018-06-23

# New Zealand Cricket Privacy Policy

New Zealand Cricket takes your privacy seriously and is committed to protecting your personal information.

The Privacy Statement outlines how we collect, use and disclose personal information when you use our site or enter competitions. This site and its content have been created in accordance with the laws of New Zealand.

### Collection of information

When you register on the website to receive a newsletter or become a member or enter a competition, we collect your personal data such as your name, address, email address and telephone number. 

We also collect information from third parties if you opt to receive information from New Zealand Cricket, e.g. Ticketek.

### Use of information

If you choose to provide us with Personal Information it will be used to deliver the information, products or services, newsletters, competition entries and offers you request or which we think may be of interest to you and subject to any preferences you indicated.

We may disclose your information to organisations involved in cricket or sporting initiatives in New Zealand, such as the Major Associations or Districts or companies we have engaged to carry out activities on our behalf.

### Opt out

If you no longer wish to receive newsletters, offers or information, please contact us at [info@nzcricket.org.nz](mailto:info@nzcricket.org.nz) or by post to the following address, New Zealand Cricket, PO Box 958, Christchurch at any time to exercise your opt-out rights.

### Information retention

The information we collect will be retained for the duration of your subscription for the purposes of contacting you.

### Security and storage

We will ensure that all of the information you supply is held securely in accordance with data protection laws and regulations. We take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification or unlawful destruction or accidental loss of Personal Information.

### Site traffic and cookies

When you visit our website, we may automatically download short text files called “cookies” to your computer. Cookies enable us to provide you with a better online experience by enabling the site to know that you have visited before and in some cases to record preferences in order to personalise your visit. Cookies also assist us to analyse the profile of our visitors. Cookies do not identify the individual user, but only the computer that is being used to view the site. These can be session cookies which are deleted when you close your browser and/or persistent cookies which remain on your computer for a longer period of time.

### Access to your data

You are entitled to obtain confirmation of whether or not we hold any personal information about you and to obtain access to that information.  You may request the correction of your personal information at any time.  We will inform you of any steps taken by us in response to your request for a correction.

If you have any question about your personal information or want to amend your details you can contact us at:

New Zealand Cricket  
PO Box 958   
Christchurch

Email: [info@nzcricket.org.nz](mailto:info@nzcricket.org.nz)

### Third Party Websites

This site may contain links to third party websites The links are for your convenience and are not governed or endorsed by us.  New Zealand Cricket has no control of either the content or the privacy policies of these third party websites and encourages users to review such policies prior to submitting any personal information to them.

### Updates to our information practices

From time to time we make changes to our information practices or alter the functionality of our website.  We always update this statement accordingly, so we encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on privacy practices at New Zealand Cricket.

If you have any questions about our privacy policies or any other matter, please contact us.
